

WORK EXPERIENCE

SUPERVISOR - XOC'OLIVE (Barcelona)

August 2018 - June 2020

COOK / SERVER - Restaurante Tomoe (Barcelona)

January 2018 - August 2018

SHOP ASSISTANT - Restaurante La Terrenal (Barcelona)

February 2017 - December 2017

EVENT PHOTOGRAPHER - Zero Cloud (Tokyo)

August 2015 - July 2016

HOSTESS - Pepa Cafe Forest (Tokyo)

August 2015 - July 2016

ASSISTANT PHOTOGRAPHER - Tobi Asmoucha (Toronto)

October 2014 - June 2015

HOSTESS - Trattoria Tavernitti (Toronto)

March 2014 - June 2015

COOK / SERVER - Salt Wine Bar (Toronto)

June 2012 - December 2013

COOK / SERVER - Loft Dining Gu (Tokyo)

June 2008 - March 2012

ABILITIES

Very Fast Learner Attention to detail

Adaptability

Flexibility

Dedicated Self-starter

Able to see multiple perspectives

CONTACT

P: +34 640 835 895 E: kaye.miyajima@gmail.com

KEI MIYAJIMA

https://react-portfolio-keimiyajima.netlify.app/

ABOUT

Highly motivated and hard-working individual with more than 8 years of experience of working abroad. Self-taught programmer, always eager to learn new things to be resourceful.

Seeking any challenging position to start and gain experience in the professional programming environment.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Self-learning| July 2020 - Current

DIPLOMA OF INDEPENDENT DIGITAL PHOTOGRAPHY with Honors Seneca College, Ontario, Canada | 2014-2015

BACHELOR OF ARTS, AMERICAN HISTORY

Rikkyo University, Tokyo, Japan | 2008–2012

LANGUAGES

JAPANESE: Native Language

ENGLISH: Fluent (speaking, reading, writing)

SPANISH: Conversatiional Level

SKILLS

Programming Skills



Other Skills

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom Microsoft Office